http://www.celebritydetective.com/privacy.html

CelebrityDetective.com is committed to protecting your privacy. All information that you share is confidential. CelebrityDetective.com only has access to limited personal information. CelebrityDetective.com only requests that an e-mail address is provided by the purchaser in order to process the transaction. Purchaser e-mail addresses are made available by PayPal. CelebrityDetective.com will not share your e-mail address with any outside parties and will never send you unsolicited e-mail.
Credit Card Numbers, Check Card Numbers, Bank Account Numbers Collected by PayPal
CelebrityDetective.com does not have access to credit card numbers, check card numbers or bank account numbers; this information is collected and retained exclusively by PayPal. PayPal provides this message regarding your personal information:
"We protect your information using physical, technical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the safeguards we use are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to data centers, and information access authorization controls." You can learn more about how PayPal handles personal information here: https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full#How_We_Protect_and_Store_Personal_Information.
Links
CelebrityDetective.com contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Home | Health & Beauty | Athlete Houses | Music Houses | Actors Houses | Athlete Addresses | Music Addresses | Actors Addresses | Privacy Policy | Amazon Affiliate Disclosure
Top of page
We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.
